

### **ABOUT ME**

My name is Ian Jackson and I am a Graphic Designer and Web Developer.

Backed with 10 years of experience working in the marketing industry, I aim to create stunning and practical designs to help connect you with your audience. Whether you need a new logo or a website, an event flyer or landing page, it's my job to dig into your needs and find creative solutions to your problems.

Over the course of my career I have worked with major brands like Harley-Davidson and MasterCraft Boats, D1 college athletics, and smaller mom & pop businesses and would love to add you to this list.

# CONTACT

239.405.9711

ijacksondesign@gmail.com . . . . . .

# ianjacksondesign.com

# **SKILLS**

- Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, After Effects
- Layout Design
- Typography
- Branding
- Photography
- HTML/CSS

# IAN JACKSON GRAPHIC + WEB DESIGN

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### PARR MOTO | GRAPHIC DESIGNER Fort Myers, FL | 2014-2020

- Producing seasonal retail marketing assets for in-store and online usage for the entire U.S. Harley-Davidson dealership network
- Working with a team of account executives and project managers to meet client needs and deadlines
- Delivering final print files and proofing prints

#### MUD READY APPAREL | OWNER Lehigh Acres, FL | 2015-2018

- Developing brand identity and merchandise
- Designing and maintaining webstore and ensuring inventory is kept up-to-date
- Creating promotional graphics to be shared across social channels

#### CUSTOMTEESNOW | PRINT ARTIST Naples, FL | 2015-2016

- · Preparing artwork for screenprinting
- Creating custom designs for customers that don't have their own artwork
- Communicating with customers about their art and working with them to receive final approval before printing
- Proofing test prints to ensure proper placement and colors

#### FGCU ATHLETICS | GRAPHIC DESIGN INTERN Fort Myers, FL | 2012-2015

- Collaborating with the marketing department to produce game day materials such as event flyers, newspaper ads, social posts, billboards, and schedule cards & magnets
- Developing wall wraps for various facilities around the sports complex
- Laying out donor sponsorship proposal packages

# **EDUCATION**

#### UCF CODING BOOTCAMP

Orlando, FL | 2020-present

#### FLORIDA GULF COAST UNIVERSITY

Fort Myers, FL | 2011-2015 | Art BA